welcome to highways news this is
vijakbar the non-life insurance business
of bharti aksar general insurance
company limited bharti exa acquisition
by icici lumbar general insurance
company limited has been approved by
insurance regulatory and development
authority of india the communication
later dated september 3 2021 has granted
its final approval with respect to the
state transaction
the proposed transaction is expected to
result in value creation for all
stakeholders throw meaningful revenue
and operational strategies further
policyholders and partners should
benefit from an enhanced product suit
and deeper customer correct touch points
the employees of the combined business
will also benefit by a greater
opportunities across functions and
geographies thank you for watching hibis
news
you